[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Shadow Punisher]
[Divine Constable Tally]
[Episode 12]
Any more bets?
Any bets?
Come on.
Hurry up.
Wolf cub,
whether I can
win big this time
depends on you.
Great! Go!
Have you seen enough?
Tiesha! Tiesha! Tiesha!
Tiesha!
Jiuying!
Oh no.
At this rate, she'll die.
Don't worry.
Look,
that kid's breathing
is completely steady.
Tiesha! Tiesha! Tiesha!
Tiesha is amazing!
So amazing!
Tiesha! Tiesha!
Is that enough?
Jiuying!
Tiesha! Tiesha! Tiesha!
She showed mercy just now.
Otherwise, what got slit
wouldn't be his ear,
but his throat.
You can do that?
Jiuying!
Come on!
Watch out, Jiuying!
Dodge, Jiuying!
Something's wrong.
Xia Jiuying,
use the collar on your neck!
What's that about?
Master, you were right.
Good.
Move! Move!
Get out of the way! Move!
Good.
Get up.
Get up!
Master said
you fought well in this match.
This is your reward.
Is that gold?
Really?
Yes.
The boss is generous.
Everyone,
our master
has always been fair in rewards and punishments.
As long as the job is done beautifully,
there will be heavy rewards.
Our Master also said,
from now on,
Xia Jiuying
will be the Hound Pit's
first-class boxer!
Great!
So amazing!
Yeah,
a first-class boxer!
Great!
Good food and drinks
will be provided!
Let me tell you,
this girl
still has many powerful moves
she hasn't used yet.
In the future,
if you want to see more,
please continue to support us.
Great! Great! Great!
Xia Jiuying! Xia Jiuying! Xia Jiuying!
Xia Jiuying! Xia Jiuying!
-Great! -Awesome!
These animals.
Why is she leashed up again?
Move.
Good job.
Well fought.
That was impressive.
I'll bet on her next time.
Exactly. She's amazing.
Let's go.
Let's go back and see.
You can't judge a book by its cover.
I'll definitely bet on her in the next few matches.
Young Master.
Who are you?
Just a fated stranger.
Seeing your elegant demeanor,
you are definitely no ordinary person.
May I know
where your home is, Young Master?
I have never seen you before.
You are not from Mingling County.
Tianhuang City,
[Divine Constable, Qingyang]
Divine Constable Bureau.
A Divine Constable from the Divine Constable Bureau?
[Divine Constable Tally]
The bureau that solves every case,
enforces the law impartially,
and punishes evil?
Exactly.
I am Gong Le.
I apologize for my offense just now.
Lord Divine Constable,
please
save my friend.
Stand up and speak.
The friend you mentioned,
is it
Xia Jiuying?
Exactly.
I came to you
precisely to ask about her.
Whatever you want to know, My Lord,
I will tell you everything.
Then tell me
how she entered the Ji Mansion
and became a servant.
Actually, when I met Jiuying,
she had already entered the Ji Mansion
as a servant.
Her father died early.
She lived
with her mother in the mountains.
When she was 5,
her mother went into the mountains to look for sheep
and never came back.
People say her mother
was bitten to death by wolves.
But I don't think so.
Jiuying told me
when she went into the mountains to look for her mother,
she took a big fall.
It was a wolf that saved her.
From then on,
she ate and lived
with the wolves.
She also said
the wolves helped her look for her mother.
It's just that this search lasted for 12 years.
No wonder Xia Jiuying's habits
are so similar to wolves.
Living with wolves,
Jiuying gradually
developed
great hunting skills.
Once,
Ji Ada went hunting in the mountains
and met Xia Jiuying.
Impressed by her skills,
he took her into the Ji Mansion
as a servant.
Let me ask you,
do you know
about Xia Jiuying digging up corpses
in the Corpse Forest Graveyard?
Digging up corpses?
Didn't she tell you about it?
Young Master.
Divine Constable.
Young Master,
I was looking everywhere for you.
The Old Madam lost her temper again,
asking where you were.
Master asked you
to hurry back to the manor.
So,
you're the young master of the Gong family.
Please forgive my disrespect.
My Lord,
you saw it too.
The Ji Mansion is forcing Jiuying to fight.
They order her around
like an animal
and even force her to sleep in a dog cage.
My Lord,
I beg you to save Jiuying,
even if it means taking her away from here.
Young Master.
Young Master,
Master and Old Madam are both in the manor,
waiting for you.
Master?
As far as I know,
isn't the Gong family
managed by Old Madam Gong?
You may not know this, My Lord.
Seventeen years ago,
the Gong family suffered a great disaster.
Seventeen years ago?
What happened 17 years ago?
Seventeen years ago,
there was a great plague in Mingling.
All 13 members of the Gong family
passed away.
Only my grandmother and I are left.
My uncle is a distant relative of the Gong family.
The old lady
has been in poor spirits ever since,
so she handed over
all the affairs of the household
to Master Gong Sihai
to manage.
Young Master,
we'd better go back quickly.
Don't let the Master and the Old Madam
wait too long,
Young Master.
My Lord,
we'll take our leave.
Let's go.
Hurry, let's go.
Jiuying must be secretly digging
for her mother's corpse.
Young Master.
Let's go, let's go!
Hurry.
I see.
It seems
I must pay a visit to the Ji Mansion.
[Ji Mansion]
My Lords,
this is our Ji Mansion.
Mind the steps.
This way.
Who is that person?
That is our Second Master.
Second Master?
So Boss Ji
has a twin brother.
Our Second Master
has been frail and sickly since childhood.
He is in poor health
and rarely goes out.
Gentlemen,
this way, please.
Master.
Master,
the lords have arrived.
Divine Constables, welcome to my humble abode.
Forgive me for not greeting you sooner.
Gentlemen,
please take a seat.
Boss Ji, you are being modest.
How can this place be a humble abode?
I originally thought
that in Mingling,
the shipping magnate Gong family was second to none.
I really didn't expect that
you're the one who's keeping a low profile,
hiding your wealth,
and making a fortune in silence.
You are handsome
and extraordinary.
You must be the world-famous
Divine Constable, Qingyang.
Divine Constable, you must be joking.
I only do a bit of
small business.
I was able to build up this meager family business
thanks to
the blessing of the current Princess Ding.
Boss Ji, you are being modest again.
How is this considered a small business?
You're selling rice on the surface
and running underground fighting rings.
I think,
when it comes to making money
through any means necessary,
no one can beat you, Boss Ji.
Men,
serve tea.
No need.
We don't have time to drink your tea.
You must be
Constable Iron, Lord Yan.
Thank you for your help
at the dock today.
I am
extremely grateful.
[Prosperous and Flourishing]
Boss Ji.
Today at the Hound Pit,
to attract gamblers,
you deliberately arranged
for a young girl to fight.
Do you know this is an immoral way to make money
and a total disregard for human life?
You are mistaken, My Lady.
You all saw it.
That girl today
not only wasn't beaten to death,
but she also won.
Besides,
she fought in the ring
completely voluntarily.
She was even rewarded with a gold pendant afterwards.
[Prosperous and Flourishing]
Moreover,
she is a servant of my Ji family.
Her life belongs to my family.
Does it matter
if she fights a round?
In your eyes,
is a servant's life
not a life?
Heaven, be my witness!
Back then,
her mother was bitten to death by wolves.
If I hadn't gone hunting in the mountains
and happened to come across her,
no one would have collected her body.
I took her in as a servant
precisely because she was alone and helpless.
She was truly pitiful,
so I wanted to give her a bite to eat.
Why is it that in your words,
I have become a villain?
You collected Xia Jiuying's mother's body?
She is still looking for her mother's remains.
Why didn't you tell her
where she is buried?
She is just a fool!
She's already dead.
What's the use of a pile of bones?
Mount Fuyao is so big,
who remembers
where she is buried?
Boss Ji, what you said
makes so much sense.
So,
if one day
you die an unnatural death,
and someone digs up your grave
to scatter your remains,
it wouldn't matter either.
Right?
Divine Constable Qingyang.
Even if you are from the Divine Constable Bureau,
how can you curse me like that?
Isn't this what Boss Ji
just said yourself?
Since she's dead,
what's the use of her bones?
Didn't he say that himself?
-Second Master. -Get out of the way!
Second Master.
This is my home.
Why can't I walk around?
-Master doesn’t allow you to walk around. -I want to see the Divine Constable.
Second Master!
-Let's go back. -Divine Constable!
-Let's go back, Second Master. -Divine Constable!
My Lords.
That is my younger brother.
He has a chronic illness.
Normally, he's not allowed to interfere
in any affairs in the mansion.
I don't know what's wrong with him today.
I'm afraid he might offend you, My Lords.
I must go check on him first.
Since Boss Ji has family matters
to deal with,
we won't
bother you anymore.
Boss Ji, after you settle your brother,
come to the county office.
There is something we need to confirm.
Okay.
Well, Qingyang,
you were really not polite
to Boss Ji.
This man is greedy
and shameless.
I was actually being polite
to him just now.
Let's go.
[Remain At Ease]
There's no need!
How many times have I told you?
You are not allowed to meddle in the mansion's affairs.
Brother.
Is it true that you secretly opened a gambling den?
Close it.
I will go plead with the Divine Constable Bureau.
-Considering Princess Ding's... -I told you, there's no need!
Those officials from Tianhuang City
won't make trouble
for our Ji family
over a mere gambling den.
Brother.
We cannot do things
-that violate the law. -Shut up!
Yun.
[Old Madam Gong]
Hao.
Chen.
Chen...
Grandma.
What are you yelling for?
Didn't you hear
my children talking?
They said they were tired
and wanted to
lie down and get a good sleep.
Who are you?
Grandma,
I am your grandson,
Gong Le.
Why did you run out again?
Old Madam, Old Madam.
Didn't we agree?
If you refuse to listen
and continue to run around,
then your grandson
will have to take a beating for you.
Old Madam, watch out.
The whip might hit you.
Stop hitting him.
Stop hitting
my grandson...
My grandson.
M-My grandson!
S-Stop hitting him!
Stop it!
I... I was wrong.
I was wrong. Stop hitting him.
I'm scared.
-Take Old Madam away -I’m scared!
for some rest.
Let's go, Old Madam.
N-No.
Don't look anymore.
-I’m scared. -Let’s go back and rest.
Stop hitting him.
[Coroner's Office]
Zhe Shan.
That's right.
He is Zhe Shan.
Are you sure?
I recognize his clothes.
He also developed cauliflower ears
from the numerous injuries
he sustained in the fighting ring.
No need to look.
It's him.
You just said
he didn't drown.
Then,
how exactly did he die?
Regarding this question,
we also want to know.
That's why we invited you here, Boss Ji.
Zhe Shan
was a first-class boxer of the Ji family.
You must know
something about him, right?
Of course.
Zhe Shan was an old member of my household.
He had been with me for many years.
Other than being fond of picking fights
and bragging,
he didn’t have any major faults.
However,
he was highly skilled.
To expand the Hound Pit's business,
I let him fight in the ring.
Oh, right.
He did have a habit.
Whenever he won money from fighting,
he'd go to Yulu Hall in town
to drink with women,
and wouldn't return until late at night.
So annoying.
Make sure you come on time.
You must come.
-What nonsense about being invincible? -Remember to miss us.
I, Zhe Shan, am invincible in the world!
-Who dares to disagree? -Normally,
with Zhe Shan's skills,
ordinary people
couldn't even get close to him.
Only when he was walking alone and drunk
was it the best time to strike.
To destroy the evidence,
the killer then
threw the body into the Yan River.
Boss Ji.
That's a very good deduction.
As for who the killer is,
it's hard to say.
After all, over the years,
Zhe Shan defeated
countless people.
Since they couldn't beat him openly,
they could only
resort to dirty tricks in the dark.
Boss Ji.
Did Zhe Shan and Gong Sihai
have any grudges?
Gong Sihai?
Do you mean
Gong Sihai killed Zhe Shan?
This is an official questioning.
Just answer the question.
Stop overthinking.
You all saw what happened
at the dock that day.
The Gong family has always been bullies,
especially the subordinates.
They always act out of line.
Every time, Zhe Shan stepped forward
to teach them a lesson.
Isn't that a slap in the face to them?
In my opinion,
Gong Sihai must have
felt that my men
were more capable than his,
so he deliberately took revenge
and killed Zhe Shan.
It's not
impossible.
Thank you for making the trip, Boss Ji.
Go back and rest early.
I'll take my leave.
My Lords,
if there is anything
I can do for you,
just let me know.
Outside Mingling County,
I can't say for sure.
But in this territory,
I still have the final say.
[Coroner's Office]
Master.
Bah! Who do you think you are?
[Coroner's Office]
Our county magistrate has the final say.
My Lord.
You asked me to check
the travel permit records
for people coming from Tianhuang City to Mingling County
in the 20th year of Hongyun.
I looked through them several times,
and none of the permits
had the seal of the Ministry of War.
No travel permits?
Without permits, could it be
that they went straight into the mountains?
Well...
Mingling County is small,
and there are no military camps or city defenses around.
It's reasonable for the Ministry of War officials
from Tianhuang City
to not visit for months.
Also,
there was an epidemic in the county that year.
It was impossible for outsiders to move
to our county at that time...
Except for the Ji family.
The Ji family?
The Ji family also moved to Mingling County
in the 20th year of Hongyun?
Yes.
The county annals can't be wrong.
My Lord.
As for the travel permit,
I will look into the records from other months.
No need.
I will keep an eye on this matter myself.
[Mingling County Government]
Xiu Niang.
Master.
Instead of taking care of the Second Master at home,
what are you doing here?
Master.
Brother.
Second Brother.
Why are you here?
I was worried about you.
How many times have I told you
not to meddle in external affairs?
But today is different.
The Divine Constable Bureau is here this time.
[Mingling County Government]
Why did they have to come
at this exact moment?
Brother.
Do you think
something happened to His Highness Prince Ding
and Her Highness—
Insolent!
Ji Lao'er.
You are cursing our Ji family
and me!
Go back in!
What are you looking at?
Back to the mansion!
[Mingling County Government]
Are you aware of
the Ji family's Hound Pit?
As the local magistrate,
how could I be unaware?
I've tried shutting it down.
But every time the case was reported to
the Prefect,
it got silenced.
About
Ji Ada's deduction just now,
what do you think of it, Lord Situ?
I think what he said makes sense.
There are 2 points.
First, the time
and place of the murder.
Second, the killer dumped the body in the Yan River.
What do you think?
There are 2 suspicious points in Ji Ada's words.
First,
Zhe Shan died from a beast tearing his throat,
not from a sharp weapon.
Therefore,
someone must have set the dog on him that night.
The killer indeed dumped the body in the Yan River.
But,
from the alley behind Yulu Hall
to the Yan River in Mount Fuyao,
it's nearly a 10 km walk.
Even if the killer had great stamina
and could carry the body,
how
could he ensure that
no one saw him along the way?
Look at this build.
Even if it were me,
I'd not be able to carry this body
over the mountains for 10 km
in a single sitting,
let alone have the strength to dispose of it.
Did the killer
use a carriage?
Lord Situ.
Who in the county owns a carriage?
Those who can afford a carriage in the county
are all wealthy families.
Great.
After investigating around,
it seems we have to go back to the Gong family.
But I think
the Ji family's Hound Pit is also a bit suspicious.
Why don't we
split up tonight
and investigate the Gong and Ji families?
How about it?
Okay.
[Gong's Ancestral Hall]
Where did the dog go?
I was going to start
with the Black Silk Leopard.
Why is it gone?
Let's look around.
It should be nearby.
Oh my God.
Such a big one.
No wonder Ji Ada was greedy for it.
Why does it
keep staring at me
without barking?
It's thinking about
how much force it needs
to crush your throat.
Why bite me
and not you?
Good thing I came prepared.
What is that?
My master's special knockout drops.
If it doesn't fall, I lose.
Let's go check the room.
Look.
Doesn't the person in the attic just now
look like Gong Le?
It seems we are
destined to return empty-handed this time.
Before anyone finds us,
let's go back quickly.
Obviously,
this backyard
hasn't been cleaned for years.
There are no stone bricks on the ground,
and weeds are overgrown.
But if you look closely,
there are
a few paths formed on the ground
by years of trampling.
That's right.
A path is formed by those who walk it.
Then where...
Does this one lead to?
Let's go see.
Brother,
don't blame me.
I'm doing this
all for you
and the Ji family.
Go, go.
Hurry up and go.
Don't come back once you leave.
Go, go, go.
Who are you?
Why are you locked up here?
You are just like them.
Hurry up and go.
Go, go!
Go, quickly!
I've already set
this Hound Pit on fire.
Our Ji family
will never do this kind of business again.
Go, quickly!
If you don't go now, it'll be too late.
Who's there?
Go!
Second Master?
Let them go!
Oh no, there's a fire!
The rice shop is on fire!
Put out the fire quickly!
Quick, fetch water!
Fire! Quick!
Fire!
[Rice Shop]
Water is here! Water is here!
Why did it
have to catch fire now?
I didn't expect
that in the Gong Mansion,
there would be a lake like this.
Let's go in and take a look.
Only dry bread and watery porridge.
Such a deserted garden
doesn't need guards.
Who would be living here?
It looks
more like an imprisonment.
Hao,
Chen,
you must be tired.
Lie down and get some rest.
Old Madam.
Chen...
Hao!
I know you.
Chen!
Hao!
They are not
your sons at all!
Hao...
Chen...
My father and the others are already dead.
She is your grandmother, Old Madam Gong.
Ever since I can remember,
my grandmother has been mad.
She doesn't understand anything.
Didn't she just mistake you
for her sons?
Although we outsiders
have no right to interfere in the Gong Mansion's affairs,
how can you treat
your own grandmother like this?
It's not up to me.
Then it's Gong Sihai's doing.
Reda said that
on this vast sea,
any ship flying the Gong flag
belongs to Old Madam Gong.
Your grandmother
is the true
shipping magnate of the Southeast,
and the head of the Gong Mansion.
But as a cousin who took power,
isn't Gong Sihai
overstepping his bounds
and turning his back on his family?
Divine Constable,
you kept mentioning the Gong Mansion.
But this entire Gong Mansion
no longer belongs to the Gongs.
Who hit you?
Was it Gong Sihai?
You just said
the mansion doesn't belong to the Gongs.
What do you mean?
My Lords,
actually, Gong Sihai is...
Hurry, surround this place!
Come on!
Hurry!
My Lords,
there are too many of them.
You should run first.
I'll distract them.
Let's split up.
Okay.
Hurry!
The thieves are in this garden!
Go after them!
-Stop! -Stop!
Hurry!
-Stop! -Stop running!
Stop!
After them!
-Stop running! -Stop!
[This Sihai is fake He's illegally selling official salt]
This Sihai is fake. He's illegally selling official salt.